Pennsylvania Governor's Commission to Revise the Public Employe Law of Pennsylvania Audio-Visual Materials 5199 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Pennsylvania Governor's Commission to Revise the Public Employe Law of Pennsylvania Audio-Visual Materials
1964-1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Pennsylvania Governor's Commission to Revise the Public Employe Law of Pennsylvania
5199 AV
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
Pennsylvania Governor's Commission to Revise the Public Employe Law of Pennsylvania audio recordings of discussions between members of the Hickman Commission and some other miscellaneous conversations
7919414
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 15, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5199: Pennsylvania Governor's Commission to Revise the Public Employe Law of Pennsylvania Statements, Hearings, Minutes, and Stenographic Reports of Public Hearings 5199 mf: Pennsylvania Governor's Commission to Revise the Public Employe Law of Pennsylvania on Microfilm
Pennsylvania -- Officials and employees; Pennsylvania Governor's Commission to Revise the Public Employee Law
7919414
- Robert Howlett, Michigan, 1968; 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  questions and answers from Board, June 5, 1968, Michigan Public Sector Law
- Howlett (conclusion), 1968; 2 (Box 1)
  Arvid Anderson, Statement, question and answers, June 5, 1968, Public Sector Law in New York City
- Arvid Anderson (conclusion), 1968; 3 (Box 1)
  Andrew Purcell, Pa. Assoc. of Firefighters, Dennis Nicholson, Fraternal Order of Police, June 5, 1968, Public Employee Law
- Hickman Co. Members, Discussions, 4 (Box 1)
  Interim Report by Committee
- Hickman Commission and Wilkes Barre, area Organization, 1968; 5 (Box 1)
  Hearings, Wilkes Barre, May 28, 1968
- Hickman Co. Members, 1968; 6 (Box 1)
  June 17, 1968 (evening)
- Hickman Co. Members, 1968; 7 (Box 1)
  June 17, 1968
- Hickman Commission Members, 1968; 8 (Box 1)
- Hickman Commission Members, 1968; 9 (Box 1)
- Members of Hickman Commission, 1968; 10 (Box 1)
  Review & Deliberations, June 17, 1968, Agency Shop, Nature of Labor Board
- Hickman Commission, Members, 1968; 11 (Box 1)
  Review & Deliberations, June 17, 1968, Elections, Appropriate Unit
- Members of Hickman Commission, 1968; 12 (Box 1)
  Review and Deliberations, June 17, 1968, Elections, Appeals to Elections, Scope of Bargaining
- Members of Hickman Commission, 1968; 13 (Box 1)
  Review and Deliberations, June 17, 1968, Scope of Bargaining, Compensation for Neutrals
- Hickman Commission Members, 1968; 14 (Box 1)
  Review and Deliberations, June 18, 1968
- Hickman Commission Members, 1964; 1 (Box 2)
  Review & Deliberations, June 18, 1964
- Hickman Co. Members, 1968; 2 (Box 2)
  Reviews & Deliberations, June 18, 1968